https://www.masterspring.com/about-us/order-details/#credit_terms

708.453.2570
Request a Quote »
Search for:
708.453.2570
Request a Quote
Toggle navigation
Custom Springs »
Torsion Springs
Extension Springs
Compression Springs
Coil Springs
Custom Wire Forms »
Utility Hooks, S-Hooks & J-Hooks
Tech Resources »
Useful Links
Industries Served »
Renewable Energy
Case Studies »
About Us »
Order Details & Credit Terms
Contact Us »
Search for:
Master Spring Order Details
From first piece approval to order terms, find answers to your spring
and wire form ordering questions.
Request a Quote
First Piece Approval and Order Terms
The links below will help answer some of your ordering questions. See the Technical Resources page for answers to your design questions.
Quote Prep Checklist (PDF)
First Piece Sample Approval
Order Terms (New Page)
Credit Terms & Credit Application
Download the Quote Preparation Checklist (PDF)
First Piece Sample Approval Before Running Entire Order:
If you want to verify that we can make your part per your print before we run the entire order, we can send you 5 to 10 parts (without plating) and the first piece inspection report.  You can inspect the samples to verify they match the print, and then call us back the same day you received the samples to give us approval to run the order.  This way, we hold the machine for less than 24 hours while the parts are delivered to you.  If you will need more than 1 day to approve samples, you should place an order for prototypes or samples.
Any design changes after seeing samples may result in additional charges.  For example, if your design change can be handled by a small change in material feed length, there most likely would be no extra charge.  If you decide to change material type, wire diameter, load or force, or number of bends, any of these significant design changes most likely would result in an extra charge.
Prototype or Sample Orders
If you are testing your design to make sure the spring or wire form is going to function as designed, you will need to place a prototype or sample order.  This will give you time to test the prototype.  You may decide to place another prototype order to test design changes (such as material type, wire diameter, load or force, or number of bends).  See Rapid Prototyping for more information.
Credit Terms
Credit approval is required for all new customers unless you are paying by credit card (VISA, Mastercard, or AMEX).
To establish credit with Master Spring & Wire Form Co., please fax (708-453-6420) or mail your credit application.  The application should include the company names, addresses, contact names, telephone and fax numbers of your bank and at least three trade references.  Also include your bank account number.  Please have an authorized representative of your company sign the application giving approval to your bank to release credit information.
If you don’t have your own credit application, you can download, print, and complete this PDF file.
We will notify you when your credit is approved.
Download the Credit Application (PDF)
REQUEST A QUOTE TODAY
Name*Email*
CompanyPhoneQuantities: e.g. 100/1000/10000Upload CAD and or PDF Files:
Tips
**CAD, STEP, and IGS files can no longer be uploaded and must be emailed to info@masterspring.com.
Comments: Please include info like application, when parts are needed, etcCAPTCHA
×
Tips
**CAD, STEP, and IGS files can no longer be uploaded and must be emailed to info@masterspring.com.
We use SolidWorks. We can view any SolidWorks document. If your file is not in SolidWorks, then please send an .IGES or .STEP file.
Please also send a .PDF file of your blueprint with your desired nominal dimensions and tolerances. If you only have a CAD model and not a dimensioned drawing, we can still quote you. However, we require a dimensioned blueprint with your order.
For questions on first piece approval, please review our Order Details page.
Send a Sample:
Master Spring & Wire Form Co.
1340 Ardmore Ave.
Itasca, IL 60143
Phone: 708-453-2570
Fax: 708-453-6420
Back to Form
We respect your privacy
×
Privacy Policy
Terms of Use of Web Site
This web site is owned by Master Spring & Wire Form Co. and is intended only for use in purchasing parts from us.
Any unauthorized use, any change of information, or any interference with the availability of or access to this web site is strictly prohibited.
This web site may contain hyperlinks to third party sites over which Master Spring & Wire Form Co. has no control and for which Master Spring & Wire Form Co. is not responsible.
NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES
This web site is provided “AS IS” without warranty of any kind, express or implied, including the implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, and non-infringement.
You agree to hold Master Spring & Wire Form Co. harmless from and you covenant not to sue for any claims based on use of this web site.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
Under no circumstances shall Master Spring & Wire Form Co. be liable for any special, exemplary, incidental or consequential damages that result from any use of or the inability to use, any content on this web site.
TRADEMARKS AND COPYRIGHTS
Nothing on this web site confers any license under any property right, including without limitation, any right in patent, trademark or copyright, of Master Spring & Wire Form Co., or any third party.
Privacy Policy
By accessing this web site you agree to the following:
INFORMATION
You understand and agree that Master Spring & Wire Form Co. may access, store and use your customer information.
We reserve the right to disclose, without notice to you, any information in our possession if required to do so by law.
This privacy policy does not apply to the use or disclosure of information that is collected or obtained by us through means other than this web site.
PERSONAL DATA
Master Spring & Wire Form Co. will use personal information provided by you for internal purposes only.
We don’t sell or otherwise distribute to others for the purpose of solicitation any information about our customers.
Although we use all reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your information, Master Spring & Wire Form Co. is not responsible for disclosure of any information due to errors in transmission or the unauthorized acts of third parties.
NON-PERSONAL DATA
This site may use cookies and collect IP addresses and domain names for site administration purposes.
© Master Spring and Wire Form Co.
1340 Ardmore Ave., Itasca, IL 60143
Phone: 708.453.2570 | Fax: 708-453-6420
